Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube
channel Yeh Bhi Jobs Update. Today's
video is going to be very important,
so please watch the video till the end.
Friends, we will meet again today with a new
vacancy. Today, your vacancy has
come out from your ICC Bank.
This recruitment has come out on your various posts.
This vacancy is going to be the
best vacancy for you people. You
can apply for this vacancy from all over India. Today, through this video,
I will tell you from when to when your forms will be
filled, what will be the application fee, what qualification will be required from you in it,
what has been asked of you in it, so
for complete information, do
watch the video till the end. If you have
not liked the video yet, then
like and share it. If you have come to the channel for the first
time, then definitely subscribe to the channel. So,
let's start the video. If we
talk about the total posts, for
how many posts your vacancy has come out, then your vacancy
was released for 12552 posts, here you had a
bumper  Vacancies have come out,
these vacancies have come out for your various posts,
here I have written the names of three posts,
your recruitment has come out for post clerk manager and other posts,
you can check in the notification
for which post you have to apply, from
when to when will your applications be filled, that is,
your online date, that is, from
when to when will your applications be filled, so your forms have already
started filling from Panch number 2022
and your forms will be filled by 8th December 2022, that is,
your last date is 8th
December 2022,
what has been kept for your application fee, so application
fee, there is no fee for almost any candidate here,
all the candidates' forms will be
filled absolutely free,
after the limit, what has been kept for you in this,
so your minimum age should be 18 to maximum
45 years, in future we will
also see reduction like OBC
candidate has only 3 years and SC
candidate has 5 years  There will be relaxation in the number of years
and what will be the salary in this, so
your salary will be from minimum 25000 to
maximum
₹118000 per month, you will get salary, your salary will be
according to your posts,
what is your qualification in this,
what are your requirements in this, then
10th 12th and graduate pass candidates are going to be
eligible for this vacancy, the
selection process means
how will you be selected in this, so your selection will be
through interview and documentation, your application is
going to be online, that is, these forms of
yours will be filled online and
not through any other medium, your job location
is Odisha but you
can apply for this vacancy from all over India, if
you are qualified for this vacancy, you are
interested in the form, then definitely apply,
how did you like the information, do
tell us in the comment section, like the video,
share it, press the bell icon so that
any of our future  Don't miss our updates.
If you have come to our channel for the first time, then
definitely subscribe to the channel
because we keep providing you the latest updates of the government
regularly.
That's all for today. See you in the next video. Till then,
Jai Hind, Jai Bharat.